- Oh my God, Becky.
Look at her butt.
It is so big.
(angelic music)
She looks like one of those
rap guys' girlfriends.
Who understands those rap guys?
They only talk to her
because she looks like a
total prostitute, okay?
I mean, her butt,
it's just so big.
I can't believe it's so round.
It's like out there.
I mean, gross.
Look, she's just so Black.
♪ I like big butts
and I cannot lie ♪
♪ You other brothers
can't deny ♪
♪ That when a girl walks in
with an itty bitty waist ♪
♪ And a round thing
in your face ♪
♪ You get sprung ♪
♪ Wanna pull up tough ♪
♪ 'Cause you notice
that butt was stuffed ♪
♪ Deep in the jeans
she's wearing ♪
♪ I'm hooked and I
can't stop staring ♪
♪ Oh baby, I wanna get with ya ♪
♪ And take your picture ♪
♪ My homeboys tried to warn me ♪
♪ But that butt you
got makes me so horny ♪
♪ Ooh, Rump-o'-smooth-skin ♪
♪ You say you wanna
get in my Benz ♪
♪ Well, use me, use me ♪
♪ 'Cause you ain't
that average groupie ♪
♪ I've seen her dancing ♪
♪ To hell with romancing ♪
♪ She's sweat, wet ♪
♪ Got it goin like
a turbo 'vette ♪
♪ I'm tired of magazines ♪
♪ Saying flat butts
are the thing ♪
♪ Take the average black
man and ask him that ♪
♪ She gotta pack much back ♪
♪ So, fellas (Yeah) ♪
♪ Fellas (Yeah) ♪
♪ Has your girlfriend
got the butt (Hell yeah) ♪
♪ Tell them to shake it
(shake it) shake it (shake it) ♪
♪ Shake that healthy butt ♪
♪ Baby got back ♪
♪ L.A. face with
the Oakland booty ♪
(upbeat instrumental music)
(record scratching)
♪ Baby got back ♪
♪ L.A. face with
the Oakland booty ♪
(upbeat instrumental music)
(record scratching)
♪ L.A. face with
the Oakland booty ♪
♪ I like them round and big ♪
♪ And when I'm throwing a gig ♪
♪ I just can't help myself ♪
♪ I'm acting like an animal ♪
♪ Now here's my scandal ♪
♪ I wanna get you home ♪
♪ And uh, double up, uh-uh ♪
♪ I ain't talking
about Playboy ♪
♪ 'Cause silicone parts
are made for toys ♪
♪ I wanna them real,
thick, and juicy ♪
♪ So find that juicy double ♪
♪ Mix-A-Lot's in trouble ♪
♪ Begging for a piece
of that bubble ♪
♪ So I'm looking
at rock videos ♪
♪ Knock-knee bimbos
walking like hoes ♪
♪ You can have them bimbos ♪
♪ I'll keep my
women like Flo Jo ♪
♪ A word to the
thick soul sisters ♪
♪ I wanna get with ya ♪
♪ I won't cuss or hit ya ♪
♪ But I gotta be straight
when I say I wanna
Uh till the break of dawn ♪
♪ Baby got it going on ♪
♪ A lot of simps
won't like this song ♪
♪ 'Cause them punks like
to hit it and quit it ♪
♪ And I'd rather stay and play ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm long
and I'm strong ♪
♪ And I'm down to
get the friction on ♪
♪ So ladies (Yeah) ♪
♪ Ladies (Yeah) ♪
♪ Do you wanna
roll my Mercedes (Yeah) ♪
♪ Then turn around
Stick it out ♪
♪ Even white boys got to shout ♪
♪ Baby got back ♪
(upbeat instrumental music)
♪ Yeah baby ♪
♪ When it comes to females ♪
♪ Cosmo ain't got nothing
to do with my selection ♪
♪ 36 24 36 ♪
♪ Ha ha, only if she's 5'3 ♪
♪ So your girlfriend
rolls a Honda ♪
♪ Playing workout
tapes by Fonda ♪
♪ But Fonda ain't got a motor
in the back of her Honda ♪
♪ My anaconda don't want none
unless you got buns, hon ♪
♪ You can do
side-bends or sit-ups ♪
♪ But please don't
lose that butt ♪
♪ Some brothers wanna
play that hard role ♪
♪ And tell you that
the butt ain't gold ♪
♪ So they toss it and leave it ♪
♪ And I pull up quick
to retrieve it ♪
♪ So Cosmo says you're fat ♪
♪ Well I ain't down with that ♪
♪ 'Cause your waist is small ♪
♪ And your curves are kicking ♪
♪ And I'm thinking
about sticking ♪
♪ To the beanpole dames
in the magazines ♪
♪ You ain't it, Miss Thing ♪
♪ Give me a sista,
I can't resist her ♪
♪ Red beans and rice
didn't miss her ♪
♪ Some knucklehead
tried to dis ♪
♪ 'Cause his girls
are on my list ♪
♪ He had game but he
chose to hit 'em ♪
♪ And I pull up quick
to get with 'em ♪
♪ So ladies, if
the butt is round ♪
♪ And you wanna
triple X throw down ♪
♪ Dial 1-900-Mix-A-Lot ♪
♪ And kick them nasty thoughts ♪
♪ Baby got back ♪
(upbeat instrumental music)
(record scratching)
♪ Baby got back ♪
(upbeat instrumental music)
(record scratching)
♪ Little in the middle
but she got much back ♪
(upbeat instrumental music)
(record scratching)
♪ Little in the middle
but she got much back ♪
(whipping sound)